Guide to the Hapgood Family Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1893-1977; Series III; 9.5; (23 boxes)
  - HUTCHINS HAPGOOD
    - Books
      - The Story of a Lover
        - Advertisements, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 642)
        - Book reviews, 1919, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 643)
          See also: Oversize, Box 48, folder 1533
      - A Victorian in the Modern World
        - Research notes, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 644-48)
        - Research notes, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 649-51)
          See also: Oversize, Box 48, folder 1534
        - Draft fragments, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 652-60)
          See also: Oversize, Box 48, folder 1535
        - Preface
          - Typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 661)
          - Page proofs, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 662)
        - Publicity, ca. 1939 (Box 25, Folder 663)
        - Advertisements, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 664)
          See also: Oversize, Box 48, folder 1536
        - Book reviews, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 665)
        - List of people who received gift copies, 1939 (Box 25, Folder 666)
      - Unidentified manuscript [possibly biography of Frank Butler]: holograph, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 667-70)
      - Miscellaneous draft fragments, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 671)
    - Plays
      - Enemies
        - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 672)
        - Draft B, typescript, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 673)
      - "Out of the Darkness"
        - Draft A, holograph, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 674)
        - Draft B, holograph, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 675)
        - Draft C, typescript, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 676)
        - Draft C, typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 677)
      - Miscellaneous draft fragments, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 678)
    - Shorter Works
      - Articles
        - Lists of articles, Partial, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 679)
        - "After the Thaw Tragedy", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 680)
        - "The American Girl", 1913 Oct 17
        - "American Railroad Directors", n.d.
        - "An Anarchist Farmer", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 681)
        - "Andrew Jackson Steps Back upon our Political Boards", 1915 Jan 11
        - "An Appeal to Clerks", n.d.
        - "An Appeal to Labor Leaders", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 682)
        - "An Appeal to Parents", n.d.
        - "Are You Hamlet?", n.d.
        - "Aristocratic New York", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 683)
        - "Art and Unrest"
        - "Art Insurgency", n.d.
        - "The Autobiography of a Shop Girl", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 684)
        - "Babe Ruth's Opportunity", n.d.
        - "The Baby", n.d.
        - "Back to Her Chains", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 685)
        - "A Banker on Clerks", 1911 Oct
        - "A Banker on Trusts", n.d.
        - "The Bath", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 686)
        - "Behind a Strike"
        - "Being in Debt"
        - "Ben the Bum", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 687)
        - "Benevolent Despotism", n.d.
        - "Better Books and Plays"
        - "Billiards and Slosson" (Box 26, Folder 688)
        - "Book Marks for Today", n.d.
        - "The Borough President", n.d.
        - "The Boss of Tammany Hall", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 689)
        - "The Boy", n.d.
        - "The Boyces and the Sneads"
        - "Brandeis on Efficiency" (Box 26, Folder 690)
        - "Brandeis on the New Haven"
        - "Brandeis on Industrial Conditions"
        - "Butler on Technocracy", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 691)
        - "Capt. Chance's Opportunity", n.d.
        - "The Caress", n.d.
        - "Carrigan's Sensible Errors", n.d.
        - "The Case of Becker", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 692)
        - "The Case of Bruere", n.d.
        - "The Case of Crane", n.d.
        - "The Case of Ismay", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 693)
        - "The Case of Mulraney", n.d.
        - "The Case of Mylius", n.d.
        - "The Case of Rosenthal", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 694)
        - "The Cause of Police Graft", n.d.
        - "Censorship, Civilization", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 695)
        - "The Censorship of Motion Pictures", n.d.
        - "The Charm of Baseball", n.d.
        - "The Charm of Baseball - II", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 696)
        - "The Charm of Children", n.d.
        - "Chase on Art Conditions"
        - "Child Labor", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 697)
        - "The Children of the Strikers", n.d.
        - "Christmas Joy", n.d.
        - "Chuck Connors", n.d.
        - "The Church and the Social Movement" (Box 26, Folder 698)
        - - (untitled), n.d.
        - - Plain Talk from the Pulpit, n.d.
        - - I. Dr. Manning's Attitude, n.d.
        - "The Church and the Social Movement" (Box 26, Folder 699)
        - - II. Two Opposite Tendencies
        - - III. A Militant Preacher, n.d.
        - "Clarence Darrow as a Radical", 1912 (Box 26, Folder 700)
        - "A Cold Enthusiast", 1913
        - "The Coming Epidemic of Infantile Paralysis", n.d.
        - "The Coming Trial of the Labor Leaders", 1912 May 10 (Box 26, Folder 701)
        - "Commissioner Stover Declares He's a Myth", n.d.
        - "A Conspiracy for Youth", n.d.
        - "Convex and Concave", 1913 (Box 26, Folder 702)
        - "Corrigan's Sensible Errors (I)", n.d.
        - "Corrigan's Sensible Errors (II)", n.d.
        - "Creative Liberty", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 703)
        - "The Crime of Stupidity", n.d.
        - "Cripples and Passivity"
        - "The Criminal Monkey": printed version in The Socialist War, 1917 Apr
          See: Oversize, Box 48, folder 1537
        - "A Critic of Society", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 704)
        - "Cultivate Your Garden", n.d.
        - "The Dance", n.d.
        - "Dangerous and Undesirable Citizens" (Box 26, Folder 705)
        - "A Day at Paterson", 1913
        - "Declares Bar Association Is Stagnant Body", n.d.
        - "A Deep Sea Analogy", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 706)
        - "Democracy and the Schools"
        - "Democracy in Industry (I)"
        - "Democracy in Industry (II)"
        - "Democratic Excitement", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 707)
        - "Direct Action", n.d.
        - "Disappointed Idealism", n.d.
        - "Divorce", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 708)
        - "Dr. David Blaustein", n.d.
        - "The Dog", n.d.
        - "A Domestic Row", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 709)
        - "Doubt", n.d.
        - "The Drama League and the National Censorship"
        - "A Dream", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 710)
        - "Education and the Social Unrest"
        - "English Folk Songs and Their Social Meaning"
        - "An Enlightened Attitude", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 711)
        - "Epictetus before Sleep", n.d.
        - "Eternal Love", n.d.
        - "European Gallantry", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 712)
        - "Evers and Chance"
        - "The Exceptional Child (I)", n.d.
        - "The Exceptional Child (II)", n.d.
        - "An Experiment in Education", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 713)
        - "Expression and the East Side"
        - "The Eye of the Needle", n.d.
        - "Facts and Feelings" (Box 26, Folder 714)
        - "The Fall of the Bowery", n.d.
        - "A Famous Unknown", n.d.
        - "A Feeble-minded Boy" (Box 26, Folder 715)
        - "Felix Schweighoffer", n.d.
        - "Fire and Revolution", 1912 Jul 11
        - "The Folly of Injustice", n.d.
        - "4,000 School Girls in Their Own Show", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 716)
        - "France's Philosophy", n.d.
        - "Frank Harris and Vaudeville"
        - "Free Speech", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 717)
        - "Free Speech in Peril, They Say", n.d.
        - "The Free University", n.d.
        - "A French Girl (I)", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 718)
        - "A French Girl (II)", n.d.
        - "Fruits of the Sabbath", n.d.
        - "The Gambler's Instinct", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 719)
        - "The Garden City Idea", n.d.
        - "Genius and Love", 1913 Oct 15
        - "The Gentleman's Newspaper", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 720)
        - "Ghetto since Gordin Died"
        - "Giovannitti Says Sabotage in Labor War is Justified", 1913 Jan 14
        - "A Girl Among Radicals - II", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 721)
        - "A Girl Among Radicals - III", n.d.
        - "Glimpses of the Moment", 1913 May 6
        - "Gloomy Moments", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 722)
        - "The Gods Are Thirsty", 1913 Oct 29
        - "The Good in the Saloon", n.d.
        - "The Greatest Labor Need", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 723)
        - "Ham and Politics"
        - "Hapgood on Hardie", n.d.
        - "Harvard", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 724)
        - "Harvard or Amherst?", n.d.
        - "Haywood's Arrest", n.d.
        - "Haywood at Henri's", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 725)
        - "He Who Comes Back", n.d.
        - "Head Lines", n.d.
        - "High School Breeds Snobs, Says Radical", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 726)
        - "Homeless Women Workers", n.d.
        - "Human Sympathy", n.d.
        - "Husbands and Wives" (Box 26, Folder 727)
        - "'I Ordered Waldo to Have Sipp Arrested' Declares the Mayor", n.d.
        - "I.W.W. Uplifts Those Ignored by the Unions", n.d.
        - "Ignominious Graft", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 728)
        - "The Impossiblist", 1912
        - "An Impression of Bergson", n.d.
        - "An Impression of Mayor Gaynor", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 729)
        - "Incidents of a Day", n.d.
        - "The Increasing Youth of Women", n.d.
        - "Individualistic Children" (Box 26, Folder 730)
        - "Industrial Democracy vs. Socialism"
        - "Innocents Abroad", n.d.
        - "Inside Labor Symposium", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 731)
        - "Institutions That Kill", n.d.
        - "'Insurgency' Now Rife in Education", n.d.
        - "Insurgent Prison", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 732)
        - "The Insurgents in Art", 1911 Oct 24
        - "The Interborough Transit Proposition", n.d.
        - "An Interesting Experiment", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 733)
        - "An Interesting Investigation", n.d.
        - "The Irish Movement", 1911 Oct 18
        - "Is It an Eternal Law?", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 734)
        - "Is Justice Justice?", n.d.
        - "Is Roosevelt an Anarchist?", n.d.
        - "Is There a Flaw in Baseball?", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 735)
        - "The Italians in New York: A Neglected Opportunity", n.d.
        - "The Jealous Wife", n.d.
        - "The Jealous Husband" (Box 26, Folder 736)
        - "Journalism and the People"
        - "The Joyous Negro", 1913 Oct 31
        - "The Kaiser's Memoirs", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 737)
        - "Knowledge and Revolution"
        - "Labor and Poetry"
        - "Labor and Understanding" (Box 26, Folder 738)
        - "A Labor Book", n.d.
        - "A Labor Organizer", n.d.
        - "A Labor Problem", n.d. (Box 26, Folder 739)
        - "Labor Rights and Privileges"
        - "Labor's Victory", n.d.
        - "The Larger Lesson", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 740)
        - "The Law and the Italians"
        - "Learning and Marriage"
        - "Let's Use Our Emotions", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 741)
        - "Letters from a Mechanic", n.d.
        - "A Liberal Radical", 1912 Jul 6
        - "The Lie", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 742)
        - "Life and Death"
        - "Life at the Armory", n.d.
        - "The Limitation of Production", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 743)
        - "The Little Irish Girl and Her Important Life"
        - "A Little Victim", n.d.
        - "A Live Bunch", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 744)
        - "The Live Line", n.d.
        - "Local German Stage", n.d.
        - "Love", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 745)
        - "Love and Technique", 1912 Aug 13
        - "Love at First Sight", n.d.
        - "The Love of Ideas", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 746)
        - "The Lovers", n.d.
        - "Low Wages and the Social Evil"
        - "Luxuries and Necessities" (Box 27, Folder 747)
        - "Mack and McGraw"
        - "The M'Namaras and the News"
        - "McSorley's Saloon", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 748)
        - "Mme Imperia Untouched", n.d.
        - "Majority and Minority Report"
        - "The Making of Criminals", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 749)
        - "Man's Egotism", n.d.
        - "A Mass Strike", n.d.
        - "Material and Art" (Box 27, Folder 750)
        - "The Mayor and the Police"
        - "The Mayor's Astuteness", n.d.
        - "The Mayor's Compromise", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 751)
        - "The Mayor's Parital Wisdom", n.d.
        - "Men and Ideas"
        - "Mental Dynamite and President Butler" (Box 27, Folder 752)
        - "Meyer London on Labor Unions"
        - "A Millionaire", n.d.
        - "Mine Owners Block the Way", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 753)
        - "Miss La Follette on the White Goods Girls", n.d.
        - "Mr. Howe and the Institute"
        - "Mr. Straus's Adviser", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 754)
        - "Mrs. Atherton on Roosevelt", n.d.
        - "Mrs. Lewisohn---Type", n.d.
        - "Mrs. Pankhurst and Fanaticism" (Box 27, Folder 755)
        - "Mrs. Pinchot on the Social Movement", n.d.
        - "The Mob Spirit", n.d.
        - "The Morning After", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 756)
        - "Mother's Love", n.d.
        - "Motion Picture Censorship", n.d.
        - "The Motion Picture Ordinance", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 757)
        - "The Movement of Society", n.d.
        - "Murphy's Vital Error", 1913 Oct 25
        - Music and the Drama: byline for Chicago Evening Post (Box 27, Folder 758)
          - [untitled articles], ca. 1904
          - See also: Seen from the Outside, Box 27, folder 792
        - "Must We Vote?", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 759)
        - "Mysterious Beauty", n.d.
        - "Narrow-minded Labor"
        - "A National Malady", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 760)
        - "The New Baby - I", n.d.
        - "The New Baby - II", n.d.
        - "A New Form of Literature", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 761)
        - "The New Idealists", n.d.
        - "The New Party and Socialism", 1912 Aug 9
        - "The New Rodins at the Museum", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 762)
        - "The New Sin", n.d.
        - "The New Spirit", n.d.
        - "A New Type of Politician", 1913 Oct 27 (Box 27, Folder 763)
        - "No Mere Mimic Fervor, That of Striker-Actors", n.d.
        - "No Unsexed Women in This Big Rally", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 764)
        - "Not Guilty and Direct Action"
        - "An Oasis in the Foreign Quarter", n.d.
        - "The Old Story", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 765)
        - "An Old-time Democrat", n.d.
        - "On Coming Back to Work", n.d.
        - "On Death", 1913 Oct 23 (Box 27, Folder 766)
        - "On Intolerance", n.d.
        - "Organized Charity" II. The Radical's Viewpoint, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 767)
        - III. The Conservative Viewpoint, n.d.
        - IV. It's Spiritual Aspect, n.d.
        - "The Ouija Board", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 768)
        - "Our Commissioners" - The Commissioner of Parks, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 769)
        - - The Commissioner of Police, n.d.
        - - The Fire Commisssioner, n.d.
        - "Our Engagements", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 770)
        - "A Paris Painter", n.d.
        - "The Passion of the Conservative", n.d.
        - "The Paterson Jail", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 771)
        - "The Pennsylvania Station", n.d.
        - "The People's Wisdom", n.d.
        - "Personality", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 772)
        - "Physical Training in Public Schools", n.d.
        - "The Picture Show", n.d.
        - "The Poet of the Bureau", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 773)
        - "A Poetic Reminiscence", n.d.
        - "Poetry and Everyman"
        - "Poetry and the Social Problem" (Box 27, Folder 774)
        - "The Poet's Arrest", n.d.
        - "Political Agility", n.d.
        - "Political Plagiarism", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 775)
        - "Politics and Art"
        - "The Poor Little Rich Man", 1913 Oct 24
        - "'Pop' Anson's Romance", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 776)
        - "A Popular Novelist", n.d.
        - "Post-Impressionist Drama", n.d.
        - "A Practical Philosopher", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 777)
        - "A Prisoner's Verses", n.d.
        - "Professor Bergson Vindicates the Clearness of His Philosophy"
        - "Progressive in Church", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 778)
        - "A Promoter of Spirit", n.d.
        - "Proposed Social Centres", n.d.
        - "Protest at School System of Czarism", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 779)
        - "Puvis de Chavannes", n.d.
        - "Quinlan and the I.W.W."
        - "Radical Changes Talked of for Our Public Schools", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 780)
        - "A Radical Minister", n.d.
        - "The Real News", n.d.
        - "The Receivers' Report", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 781)
        - "A Recognized Iniquity", n.d.
        - "Reformers--Good and Bad"
        - "Religion and Socialism" (Box 27, Folder 782)
        - "The Richeson Case", n.d.
        - "Riot and Youth", 1913 Feb 3
        - "Rodin's Message", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 783)
        - "Roosevelt and the Newspapers"
        - "Roosevelt's Opportunity" (Box 27, Folder 784)
          - I., n.d.
          - II., 1912 Jul 9
          - III., n.d.
        - "Roosevelt's Opportunity" (Box 27, Folder 785)
          - IV., n.d.
          - V., 1912 Aug 12
          - VI., n.d.
        - "Roosevelt's Opportunity" (Box 27, Folder 786)
          - VIII., n.d.
          - XII., n.d.
          - XIII., n.d.
        - "Ruling Children", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 787)
        - "The Russian Actor", n.d.
        - "The Salon", n.d.
        - "The Saloon and Civilization" (Box 27, Folder 788)
        - "The Saloon and the Salon"
        - "Says I.W.W. Ideals Would Aid Society", n.d.
        - "The School and the Neighborhood", 1912 Apr 4 (Box 27, Folder 789)
        - "School Democracy in Gaynor Charter", n.d.
        - "School Extravagance", n.d.
        - "School for Ballet Girls", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 790)
        - "The School House and the Social Centre", 1912 May 6
        - "The Schools and the People", 1913
        - "The Schools Should Aid Social Work", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 791)
        - "Science and Intuition", 1912 Oct 18
        - "The Seamen's Strike and Harvard University", 1912 Jul 10
        - Seen from the Outside: byline for Chicago Evening Post (Box 27, Folder 792)
          - "An Aspect of Hull House", 1905 Mar 17
          - "An Impression of Chicago", n.d.
          - "Men and Measures of the Campaign", 1905 Mar 30
          - See also: Music and the Drama, Box 27, folder 758
        - "Sees No Sign of Strike's Loss", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 793)
        - "A Sensitive Critic", n.d.
        - "Sex and Society"
        - "The Shooting at Hastings", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 794)
        - "Shorter Day First of All.--W.D. Haywood", n.d.
        - "Single Tax and Religion"
        - "Sleeplessness", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 795)
        - "The So-Called Poor", n.d.
        - "Social Initiative and School House Centre"
        - "Social Problems in Art", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 796)
        - "A Social Psychological Play", n.d.
        - "The Social Settlement", n.d.
        - "Socialism and Reform", 1913 Oct 28 (Box 27, Folder 797)
        - "Socialist Toleration - I", n.d.
        - "Socialist Toleration - II", n.d.
        - "The Socialists and the Social Movement" (Box 27, Folder 798)
        - "The Socialist Vote", n.d.
        - "Some Observations", n.d.
        - "Some Suggestions", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 799)
        - "The Soul and the Scientist"
        - "The Spider's Tragedy", 1913 Oct 13
        - "The Spring", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 800)
        - "Steffens", n.d.
        - "Story of Two Acrobats", n.d.
        - "Strike Pageant in the Garden", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 801)
        - "The Stikers' Pageant", n.d.
        - "The Subtle Press Agent", n.d.
        - "The Suffrage and Pretty Girls" (Box 27, Folder 802)
        - "Suffrage Fanaticism", n.d.
        - "'Sumurun' and Morality"
        - "Syndicalism and Morality" (Box 27, Folder 803)
        - "Taking Credit from Sweeney", n.d.
        - "Teachers Make Schools", n.d.
        - "The Terrible Girl", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 804)
        - "The Titanic and Human Nature"
        - "To Anybody's Boy", 1913 Oct 22
        - "To My Readers", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 805)
        - "To Socialists on the Coming Election", 1913 Oct 20
        - "To-day's Parade", n.d.
        - "Too Bad, George", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 806)
        - "Too Much Power to the Superintendents"
        - "Touching on Labor", n.d.
        - "The Trend of the Time" (Box 27, Folder 807)
          - I., n.d.
          - II., n.d.
          - III., n.d.
          - IV., n.d.
        - "The Trend of the Time" (Box 27, Folder 808)
          - V., n.d.
          - VI., n.d.
          - VII., n.d.
        - "True Democracy, a Spirit", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 809)
        - "Turkey-trotting Not the Object of Gaynor's Attack", n.d.
        - "The Twilight of McGlory", n.d.
        - "The Twilight of the Slugger", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 810)
        - "Two Kinds of Government"
        - "Two Kinds of Love" (Box 28, Folder 811)
        - "Two Mill Towns", n.d.
        - "Two Women and a Ghost"
        - "The Unseeing Artist", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 812)
        - "An Unusual Novelist", n.d.
        - "Upside Down", n.d.
        - "Vacation and Work" (Box 28, Folder 813)
        - "The Value of Human Life", n.d.
        - "The Value of Radical Movements", n.d.
        - "A Virtuous Wrong", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 814)
        - "A Visit to School", n.d.
        - "The Voice of the East Side", n.d.
        - "The Voice of Roosevelt", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 815)
        - "W. D. Haywood, Miner", n.d.
        - "The Waiters' Strike", n.d.
        - "'Wearin' o' the Green'", 1912 Mar 11 (Box 28, Folder 816)
        - "The Weather", n.d.
        - "What the Clerks Say", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 817)
          - I., n.d.
          - II., n.d.
          - III., n.d.
        - "What the Clerks Say", n.d (Box 28, Folder 818)
          - I., n.d.
          - II., n.d.
        - "What He Was and Is" (Box 28, Folder 819)
        - "What Is an Anarchist?", n.d.
        - "What Is Luxury?", n.d.
        - "What Is the Mayor's Policy?", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 820)
        - "What Is a Radical?", n.d.
        - "What Labor Men Say", n.d.
        - "What Mayor Gaynor Is Doing with the Police", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 821)
        - "What Rembrandt Says"
        - "What Schools Do for Our Girls", n.d.
        - "What We Overlook", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 822)
        - "Where Are We?", n.d.
        - "Which is Disloyal?", n.d.
        - "Who Is Good?", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 823)
        - "Whom the Gods Destroy They First Make Mad", n.d.
        - "Why?", n.d.
        - "Why Tammany Remains", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 824)
        - "Why She Is Idle", n.d.
        - "Will Flirting Disappear?", n.d.
        - "Will She Break Into Life?", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 825)
        - "Wilson and House"
        - "A Woman Suffrage Politician", n.d.
        - "The Woman Who Sees", n.d.
        - "Women in Society", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 826)
          - I., n.d.
          - II. The Camp Fire Girls, n.d.
          - III. New Sex and Domestic Relations
        - "Women in Society", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 827)
          - IV., n.d.
          - V., n.d.
        - "Women in the Convention", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 828)
        - "Would They Otherwise Die--Now", n.d.
        - "Young American Sculpture", n.d.
        - "A Young Girl's Dream", n.d. (Box 28, Folder 829)
        - "Zion", n.d.
        - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 830)
      - Book reviews
        - Dell, Floyd, Homecoming: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 831)
        - Edwards, Agnes, Old Coast Road: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 832)
        - Farris, John T., Seeing Pennsylvania: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 833)
        - Samson, Leon, Toward a United Front: printed version, 1934 Jan 21 (Box 28, Folder 834)
        - Shipley, Arthur Everett, The Voyage of a Vice-Chancellor: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 835)
        - Symes, Lillian and Clement, Travers, Rebel America: typescript (Box 28, Folder 836)
      - Essays
        - "The Advancing Hour": typescript, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 837)